(Amy:)Being left out
is a terrible feeling.
(Amy:)No one understands that
better than I do.
(Sheldon:)Hey, look at that.
(Sheldon:)Even in your example,
you're all by yourself.
(Amy:)When there was
a lice epidemic at my school,
(Amy:)everybody got it except me.
(Amy:)I tried to fool everyone
by sprinkling sugar in my hair,
(Amy:)but I just got attacked by bees.
(Sheldon:)I can just picture
them all right now
(Sheldon:)at Feynman's house,
(Sheldon:)probably discussing Schrodinger
(Sheldon:)and at the same time,
(Sheldon:)not discussing Schrodinger.
(Sheldon:)See?
(Sheldon:)They're missing out
on hilarious jokes like that.
(Sheldon:)And at the same time, not.
(Sheldon:)It reminds me of when
my stupid brother and sister
(Sheldon:)would build forts
in the living room
(Sheldon:)and wouldn't let me in.
(Sheldon:)I hated that so much.
(Raj:)You know,
(Amy:)there's nothing I can do
(Amy:)about getting you invited
to the symposium,
(Amy:)but if you wanted...
(Amy:)we could build a fort.